Logan Hall



info.tech.logan@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/loganthall



(859) 325-0371



http://portfolio.hallsoftworks.com

Summary

SUMMARY

Enthusiastic IT professional with over 12 years of experience in the field. Comfortable working with others as well as tackling issues alone, and getting the best results in either setting. Excited and ready to continue my developer journey and provide the most value I can to any company.

Experience

5 Technical Support Specialist

Kentucky Housing Corporation

Aug 2021 - Jan 2023 (1 year 6 months)

- Responsible for ticket routing and up to level 3 resolution of customer and infrastructure issues, routing an average of 20 tickets, and completing an average of 5 high level tickets, per day
- Computer imaging and deployment
- SCCM Administration and Image creation
- Provided remote and on-site support
- Performed application updates and rollouts, both client- and server side
- Worked with a team responsible for MS updates and Windows version testing
- Administered Active Directory users and computers

Information Technology Manager

Tailor Made Compounding

Nov 2019 - Aug 2021 (1 year 10 months)

- Tested and trained employees and customers on use of the custom EMR software, boosting the usage from under 50% to over 70% in one year
- Salesforce programming and report creation
- Created the IT department, resulting in less down time due to technology issues
- Adopted Asset Management system, reduced extra IT spending by 25%
- Replaced analog communications with a new VoIP system
- Implemented secure and segregated network at second company location
- Google Workspace administration
- Wordpress website administration and development

Tier 3 Support

LG&E and KU Energy LLC

Aug 2015 - Oct 2018 (3 years 3 months)

- Remote and desk-side support
- Equipment provisioning and installation
- MDT, SCCM, and Golden Image administration
- Ticket creation and routing

- Inventory management
- Thin client installation and troubleshooting
- Appsense integration
- Windows 10 testing
- Computer refreshes

Education

Nucamp Coding Bootcamp

Full-Stack Software Engineering

2022 - 2023

Contains Web Development, Front-End, and Back-end Software development. Includes languages, APIs, and frameworks such as HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Node.js, React, React Native, Python, PostgreSQL, Bootstrap. Hands-on experience with SDLC, CI/CD, DevOps, Azure, AWS, and GCP.

Skills

Agile & Waterfall Methodologies • GitHub • REST APIs • Python (Programming Language) • JavaScript • Amazon Web Services (AWS) • PostgreSQL • Big O Notation • Containerization • Software Development Life Cycle (SDLC)

Honors & Awards

- Certificate of Completion Nucamp Coding Bootcamp SQL and Data Modeling with Python
- Certificate of Completion Nucamp Coding Bootcamp
 Data Structures and Algorithms with Python
- Certificate of Completion Nucamp Coding Bootcamp
 Web Design Fundamentals